

#### Vilan Obaanii Obina

□ (+86) 13201851252 | ■ JinduWang@hotmail.com | ★ hippodu001.github.io

### About\_

I'm JinduWang, a Year 3 undergraduate in Software Engineering, Xi'an Jiaotong University. My research interests lie in Human-Computer Interaction (HCI). My research is focused on how to better understand users' intentions and improve users' experience in VR/AR/MR systems., which follows three connected threads: 1)Design and evaluate innovative input or output interaction methodologies and technologies. 2)Develop context-aware and adaptive user interfaces. 3)Understand and model user behavior

### Education

Xi'an Jiaotong University

Xi'an, China

B.Eng in Software Engineering 2020.9 - Present

**Neuromatch Academy** 

Online

DEEP LEARNING SUMMER SCHOOL 2021.7- 2021.8

### **Experience**

**Institute of Software, Chinese Academy of Sciences** 

Beijing, China

RESEARCH INTERN

2022.7 - Present

· Advisor: Prof. Teng Han

**Lenovo Research** 

Beijing, China

RESEARCH INTERN

2022.7 - Present

• Advisor: Researcher Nianlong Li

Intelligent Interaction Lab, Xi'an Jiaotong University

Xi'an, China

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

2022.10 - Present

· Advisor: Prof. Zhongmin Cai

Beijing Digital Force Field Technology Co., Ltd

Beijing, China

UNITY PROGRAMMER INTERN

2022.6

### Research.

# BendStick: Bendable Stick Controller for Enhancing Ray-Based Interactions with Virtual Objects

In progress for UIST2023

Supervisor: Researcher Nian-Long Li and Prof. Teng Han

2022.7 - Present

- Co design a bendable stick controller that provides extra input dimensions like double rays via physically bending, thus enables complex tasks like object manipulation, and its holding postures.
- Co design and develop user studies to compare the control accuracy of different holding postures and evaluate the efficiency of BendStick in spatial object manipulation.
- Develop demos to demonstrate the potential applications of BendStick.

# Context-aware AR Interfaces for Workspace with Both Virtual and Physical Displays (First author)

In progress for UIST2023

Supervisor: Researcher Nian-Long Li and Prof. Teng Han

2022.11 - Present

- Investigate previous work on context-aware interfaces in VR/AR/MR
- Design and develop and evaluate the context-aware AR display system to dynamically provide complementary information whilst we are mainly using a physical display, which includes designing layouts of AR displays, inputs(extrinsic and intrinsic), outputs and methods of the system, and user studies to evaluate.

#### **Body-Centric Mixed Reality Input Technology**

In progress for CHI2024

2022.12 - Present

MENTOR: XIANG LI(PHD. STUDENT IN CAMBRIDGE UNIV.)

- · Co build the design Space and analyze user's sense of ownership for a novel body-centric MR input technology
- · Co develop and design user stules to evaluate the novel body-centered interaction technology.

### Honors and Awards \_\_\_\_\_

-	Xi'an Jiaotong University Scholarship,	2022.11
-	Wang Shishao and Qiu Qizhen Scholarship,	2022.7
-	China Merchants Bank Scholarship,	2022.3
	China College Students' 'Internet+'Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition, Gold Prize	2022.10
-	(Project:Augmented Reality Knowledge Forest)	
-	Software Patent Certification, Apple App Store: ARKF	2022.4
-	Bluebridge Cup National Software Development Competition, Third Prize (Java Group)	2022.4
-	Tencent Cloud Practitioner Certification,	2021.11
-	National College Student Psychology Committee Top 100 Member,	2021.10

## Technical Skills \_\_\_\_\_

### **Programming**

CSHARP, JAVA, PYTHON(PYTORCH), GLSL, C/C++, OPENGL

### **Software and Tools**

UNITY3D(VR,AR), MYSQL, LATEX, USER STUDY DESIGN, VISIO